Ey.
I...
I wanted to thank you for saving us.
No, no, no. Hold on. Listen.
It's all on me.
What do you mean?
I mean, I used to work for Greg.
I thought he was the smartest guy
out there.
But your man...
He outsmarted him.
Mason gave me the fake documents.
Then I went
and handed them over to Greg.
No questions asked.
Then I...
I don't understand.
Yeah, I was just the eyes and
ears in this place.
No, I mean, I don't understand.
Why did you save us?
Don't you get it?
I love you.
I love you, Veronica.
With all my heart.
From the first day
I started working for you.
Listen, I don't need anything in return.
I know you love him.
I never gonna forgive myself
for betraying the Aspen family.